{
    "Subject": {
        "Database": [
            {
                "Option4": "Data Backup Management System",
                "Option3": "Database Migration System",
                "Option2": "Database Management System",
                "Option1": "Data of Binary Management System",
                "Question": "What is the fullform of DBMS ?",
                "identity": 1,
                "correctAnswer": "Database Management System"
            },
            {
                "Option4": "Organized collection of data that cannot be updated",
                "Option3": "Organized collection of data or information that can be accessed, updated, and managed",
                "Option2": "Collection of data or information without organizing",
                "Option1": "Organized collection of tables that cannot be accessed, updated, and managed",
                "Question": "Database is a _______________________",
                "identity": 2,
                "correctAnswer": "Organized collection of data or information that can be accessed, updated, and managed"
                
            },
            {
                "Option4": "All of the above",
                "Option3": "Data in the form of audio or videntityeo",
                "Option2": "Text, files containing data",
                "Option1": "Image oriented data",
                "Question": "Which type of data can be stored in the database?",
                "identity": 3,
                "correctAnswer": "All of the above"
                
            },
            {
                "Option4": "Data Migration Language",
                "Option3": "Data Markup Language",
                "Option2": "Data Manipulation Language",
                "Option1": "Data Management Language",
                "Question": "Full form of DML is",
                "identity": 4,
                "correctAnswer": "Data maniipulation Language"
            },
            {
                "Option4": "Sharon B. Codd",
                "Option3": "Charles Babbage",
                "Option2": "Charles Bachman",
                "Option1": "Edgar Frank Codd",
                "Question": "Who created the DBMS?",
                "identity": 5,
                "correctAnswer": "Charles Bachman"
            },
            {
                "Option4": "All of the above",
                "Option3": "Entity",
                "Option2": "Tuples",
                "Option1": "Degree",
                "Question": "Rows of a relation are known as the _______.",
                "identity": 6,
                "correctAnswer": "All of the above"
            },
            {
                "Option4": "Many teachers may have many classes",
                "Option3": "Many classes may have many teachers",
                "Option2": "One teacher can have many classes",
                "Option1": "One class may have many teachers",
                "Question": "What do you mean by one to many relationships?",
                "identity": 7,
                "correctAnswer": "One teacher can have many classes"
            },
            {
                "Option4": "Query",
                "Option3": "DDL",
                "Option2": "None of the option",
                "Option1": "DML",
                "Question": "Which of the following is generally used for performing tasks like creating the structure of the relations, deleting relation?",
                "identity": 8,
                "correctAnswer": "DDL"
            },
            {
                "Option4": "Relational schema",
                "Option3": "Query",
                "Option2": "DDL",
                "Option1": "DML",
                "Question": "Which of the following providentityes the ability to query information from the database and insert tuples into, delete tuples from, and modify tuples in the database?",
                "identity": 9,
                "correctAnswer": "DML"
            },
            {
                "Option4": "select empidentity where empidentity = 1009 and Lastname = 'GELLER';",
                "Option3": "select empidentity from emp;",
                "Option2": "select empidentity from emp where empidentity = 10006;",
                "Option1": "select * from emp where empidentity = 10003;",
                "Question": "Which one of the following given statements possibly contains the error?",
                "identity": 10,
                "correctAnswer":  "select * from emp where empidentity = 10003;"
            }
        ]
    }
}